other stock that we're looking at today
and this one is surging his ICICI
Lombard up over eight percent right now
this after ICICI Bank has decided to
raise its holding in the insurance in
the insurer by four percent so surbhi is
joining us with the details on this one
survey thanks so that's right so I say
Bank in this board meeting has approved
increasing stake in Lombard by four
percent in multiple tranches now Bank
said it would acquire at least two and a
half percent stake off the four percent
before September 9th of 2024. now just
to give you some context on this the
bank currently holds 48 stake in Lombard
and post the merger with bharti AXA
ICICI Bank had to bring down its take in
Lombard to 30 by September of 2024 but
earlier in April RBI had allowed the
most entity HDFC and HDFC Bank to hold
bones in 50 stake in HDFC life thereby
creating a precedent following which all
the eyes were on ICICI Bank on whether
they would increase the stake to 50
percent of bringing
now that they've announced that they
will increase it to 50 a big stake sale
overhang is gone from ICICI Lombard and
that's why it's urging in shade today
okay serging and how even after coming
off the highs it's still senior year
nine percent moves Ruby thanks a lot for
that